[
    {
        "front": "はは",
        "back": "Mother (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちち",
        "back": "Father (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いもうと",
        "back": "Younger Sister (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あね",
        "back": "Elder Sister (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとうと",
        "back": "Younger Brother (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あに",
        "back": "Elder Brother (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "そぼ",
        "back": "Grandmother (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "そふ",
        "back": "Grandfather (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "つま",
        "back": "Wife (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おっと",
        "back": "Husband (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすめ",
        "back": "Daughter (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこ",
        "back": "Son (mine)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おこうさん",
        "back": "Mother (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとうさん",
        "back": "Father (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いもうと",
        "back": "Younger Sister (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おねさん",
        "back": "Elder Sister (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとうと",
        "back": "Younger Brother (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おにさん",
        "back": "Elder Brother (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おばあさん",
        "back": "Grandmother (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おじいさん",
        "back": "Grandfather (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おくさん",
        "back": "Wife (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごしゅじん",
        "back": "Husband  (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすめさん",
        "back": "Daughter (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこさん",
        "back": "Son (someone else)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "りんご",
        "back": "Apple",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちご",
        "back": "Strawberry",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "もも",
        "back": "Peach",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "すいか",
        "back": "Watermelon",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "みかん",
        "back": "(Japanese) Orange",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶどう",
        "back": "Grape",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "なし",
        "back": "Japanese Pear",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かき",
        "back": "Persimmon",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "バナナ",
        "back": "Banana",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "メロン",
        "back": "Melon",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "レモｎ",
        "back": "Remon",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かみ",
        "back": "Hair",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あたま",
        "back": "Head",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "め",
        "back": "Eyes",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "みみ",
        "back": "Ears",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "はな",
        "back": "Nose",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "くち",
        "back": "Mouth",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かお",
        "back": "Face",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かた",
        "back": "Shoulders",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "うで",
        "back": "Hands",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あし",
        "back": "Legs",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おなか",
        "back": "Stomach",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "て",
        "back": "Hand, arm",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "は",
        "back": "Teeth",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "くるま",
        "back": "Car",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんしゃ",
        "back": "Train",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "じてんしゃ",
        "back": "Cycle",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "えき",
        "back": "Station",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばす てい",
        "back": "Bus Stop",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかてつ",
        "back": "Subway",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "みせ",
        "back": "Shop",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "がっこう",
        "back": "School",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎんこう",
        "back": "Bank",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "びょういん",
        "back": "Hospital",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いえ",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "うち",
        "back": "Home",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうえん",
        "back": "Park",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうしつ",
        "back": "Classroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "がくせい",
        "back": "Student",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうがっこう",
        "back": "Primary",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうがっこ",
        "back": "Middle",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうこう",
        "back": "High School",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがく",
        "back": "University",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ともだち",
        "back": "Friends",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごはん",
        "back": "Food",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょねん",
        "back": "Last Year",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ことし",
        "back": "This Year",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいねん",
        "back": "Next Year",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんげつ",
        "back": "Last  Month",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんげつ",
        "back": "This Month",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいげつ",
        "back": "Next Month",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんしゅう",
        "back": "Last Week",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんしゅう",
        "back": "This Week",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいしゅう",
        "back": "Next Week",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "にちようび",
        "back": "Sunday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "げつようび",
        "back": "Monday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かようび",
        "back": "Tuesday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "すいようび",
        "back": "Wednesday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "もくようび",
        "back": "Thursday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "きんようび",
        "back": "Friday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "どようび",
        "back": "Saturday",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "なん, なに",
        "back": "What",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "どこ / どちら",
        "back": "Where",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "だれ / どなた",
        "back": "Who",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうして / なぜ",
        "back": "Why",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "どやって / なんで",
        "back": "How",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつ",
        "back": "When",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いくら",
        "back": "How Much",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おいくつ",
        "back": "How Old",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "どれ / どの",
        "back": "Which",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゃがいも",
        "back": "Potato",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "トマト",
        "back": "Tomato",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "たまねぎ",
        "back": "Onion",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいこん",
        "back": "(Japanese) Raddish",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "にんじん",
        "back": "Carrot",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゃべつ",
        "back": "Cabbage",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうり",
        "back": "Cucumber",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "まめ",
        "back": "Beans, Peas",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "レタス",
        "back": "Lettuce",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "はくさい",
        "back": "Chinese Cabbage",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほうれんそう",
        "back": "Spinach",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "なす",
        "back": "Egg plant, Brinjal",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねぎ",
        "back": "Welsh Onion",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あまい",
        "back": "Sweet",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "からい",
        "back": "Spicy",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "さっぱい",
        "back": "Salty",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "すっぽい",
        "back": "Sour",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "にがい",
        "back": "Bitter",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "うまい",
        "back": "Tasty",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "さむい",
        "back": "Cold (Atmos.)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "つめたい",
        "back": "Cold (Obj.)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あつい",
        "back": "Hot",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほん",
        "back": "Japan",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "いんど",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごく",
        "back": "China",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんこく",
        "back": "Korea",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ろしあ",
        "back": "Russia",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "あめりか",
        "back": "America",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "イギリス",
        "back": "England",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "イタリア",
        "back": "Italy",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ドイツ",
        "back": "Germany",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "タイ",
        "back": "Thailand",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "フランス",
        "back": "France",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ブラジル",
        "back": "Brazil",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "すし",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おこのみやき",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "さしみ",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ていしょく",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんぷら",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "うどん",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "そば",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おにぎり",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎょうざ",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "みそ",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "やきにく",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "たこやき",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "みず",
        "back": "Water",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうひい",
        "back": "Coffee",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうちゃ",
        "back": "Black Tea",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "(お)ちゃ",
        "back": "Green Tea",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ジュース",
        "back": "Juice",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "みるく / ぎゅうにゅう",
        "back": "Milk",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ビール",
        "back": "Beer",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ワイン",
        "back": "Wine",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おさけ",
        "back": "Alcohol",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひこうき",
        "back": "Airplane",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "くるま",
        "back": "Car",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "じてんしゃ",
        "back": "Bicycle",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "バイク",
        "back": "Bike",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "トラック",
        "back": "Truck",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかてつ",
        "back": "Underground train",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "メトロ",
        "back": "Metro",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんしゃ",
        "back": "Electric train",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふね",
        "back": "Ship",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "タクシ",
        "back": "Taxi",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんかんせん",
        "back": "Bullet Train",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "とうきょう",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおさか",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうと",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうべ",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "なごや",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "よこはま",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふくおか",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "しずおか",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんだい",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふくしま",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    },
    {
        "front": "かなざわ",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "N5 C-Add"
    }
]